Guide to the Robert F. Metzdorf Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Robert Frederic Metzdorf autograph collection
1764-1946
MS 984
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
A collection of letters and signed documents, chiefly of United States cabinet members and other government officials.
Metzdorf, Robert F. (Robert Frederic), 1912-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Robert F. Metzdorf in the 1950s.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The letters are arranged alphabetically by personal name.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of approximately sixty letters and signed documents, chiefly of United States cabinet members and other government officials. The collection was donated to Yale University in several gifts during the 1950s by Robert F. Metzdorf, Curator of Manuscripts and University Archivist.
United States -- Politics and government; Autographs
- Inventory
  - Abbot, Benjamin, 1764 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbot, Jacob, 1829 February (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bautwell, George S., 1870 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bristow, Benjamin Helm, 1875 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cameron, James Donald, 1894 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cameron, Simon, 1833 June 4, 1861 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chase, Salmon P., 1862 March 7, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clay, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1913 March-1919 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dean, Peter V., 1839 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Everett, Edward, 1959 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fairchild, Charles, 1893 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1874 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Goddard, Edward, [ca. 1750] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graham, Charles, 1835 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Guthrie, James, 1855 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Havers, S. F., 1860 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hay, John, [190?] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1946 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hughes, Charles E., 1924 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ingham, Samuel D., 1831 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Stephen, 1816 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Longman, C. J., 1884 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - McAdoo, William G., 1917 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marcy, William L., 1853 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Noah, Mordecai M, 1830 September (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Parker, Gilbert, 1914 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Riddell, Henry Scott, 1862 Aug, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Root, Elihu, 1917 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rush, Richard, 1848 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Scott, John, 1771 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Seward, William H., 1855 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sherman, John, 1896 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Smith, William, 1863 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Spencer, John Canfield, 1926 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Spinner, Frances E., 1874 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stove, E.
    General note
    See: Folder 4
  - Wilson, Daniel, bsp. of Calcutta, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Winslow, Octavius, 1851 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Woollcott, Oliver, 1787 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)